[theme music]
♪ Ahhh ahh ahh ahhh ♪
♪ Aaah ♪
♪ Whatever happened
to predictability ♪
♪ The milkman
the paperboy evenin' TV ♪
♪ When did I get
to living here ♪
♪ Somebody tell me please ♪
♪ This whole world's
confusing me ♪
♪ Clouds as mean
as you've ever seen ♪
♪ And a bird
that knows your tune ♪
♪ Then a little voice
inside you whispers ♪
♪ Kid don't sell
your dreams so soon ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ Everywhere.. ♪
♪ There's a heart ♪
♪ A hand to hold on to ♪
♪ Everywhere you look
♪ Everywhere.. ♪
♪ There's a face
of somebody who needs you ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ When you're lost out there ♪
♪ And you're all alone ♪
♪ A light is waitin'
to carry you home ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ Chity chi bob botta ♪♪
Okay, kids, are we ready
to start Michelle's
5th birthday party?
(together)
Yay!
Wait a minute.
This is a Flintstones
caveman party.
Cave people
never say "Yay."
They say ooga-ooga.
How do you know
they said "ooga-ooga?"
Because I'm Wilma Flintstone.
I was there.
Now, if we all say
ooga-ooga, I bet we can get
the rest of
my Bedrock buddies to show up.
(together)
Ooga-ooga!
Well, ooga-ooga, everybody.
Hi, I'm, uh, Barney.
This is Betty.
We're the Rubbles.
And now, to meet the world's
only housebroken dinosaur..
...Dino!
Boom shaka-laka-laka,
boom shaka-laka-laka
boom shaka-laka-laka,
boom shaka-laka-laka, boom!
What kind of dinosaur
are you?
I'm a tidy-o-saurus.
Please, kids,
whatever you do
keep the cave floor clean.
Wilma!
Could you give me a hand
picking up these crumbs?
My arms haven't evolved yet.
Ooga-ooga, Dino.
You know, dad, the kids
really love all the props
you got to borrow
from the station.
Ah, D.J., it was real sweet
of you to dress up
and play along like this.
Well, just remember, when
I get my driver's license
I have two words
for you. Red Porsche.
And I have two words
for you. Bus pass.
Alright, alright, cave kids,
uh, it's time to bring out
our favorite 5-year-old
cave babe
Michelle Pebbles Tanner.
(together)
Ooga-ooga!
This is Comet,
my pet stegosaurus.
That's not a stegosaurus.
That's a Golden Retriever.
You got a bad attitude.
Hey, we're missing somebody.
How can we be
a modern stone age family
without Fred Flintstone?
I wouldn't do this
for anyone but Michelle.
Wilma!
(Becky)
'I'm not Wilma.'
Just practicing.
Jess.
I think it's time.
I know. Put on
your little costume.
You're gonna make
a great preg-o-saurus.
I'm gonna go get my club.
No. I mean, I think it's
time to have the babies.
No.
I think so.
Get outta here.
I really do.
No.
I think so!
Get outta here.
Jess, get a grip.
It's happening.
You know that indigestion
I've been having?
Yeah, from Joey's cocoa puff
omelets. I got it too.
Yeah, well, my pangs
of indigestion
are now coming
ten minutes apart.
Ow. So are mine.
Jess, it's not indigestion.
I know it's three weeks early,
but I'm going into labor.
What am I goin' into?
I don't know. Maybe you're
having sympathy pains.
Oh, no, no. Honey,
this is impossible.
W-we're not ready
to have the kids yet.
I didn't finish
building the nursery.
I haven't picked out the names
haven't practiced
the hospital drill.
So you can't possibly
be going into labor
because I'm not ready yet!
Well, ready or not,
here they come.
- No.
- Yes!
Get outta here.
Jess! We've already
played this game.
Now, come on. I'm ready
to have our babies.
Have mercy!
Oh, honey, we gotta
get to the hospital.
You know what? Hey, hoo-hoo.
See, I'm going to be cool.
I'm not going to be like those
jerk husbands who get all crazy
and go nuts because their
wife's going into labor.
I'm gonna be very calm,
cool and collected.
'Cause, hey, babe,
I'm there for you. I'll pack.
[snaps]
Ready!
Here. Grab an end.
Hon, we're having a baby,
not goin' to Europe.
You're right.
We got to lose something.
Alright. What do
you like better?
The blue silk or say
the black rhinestone?
Ah, for childbirth?
I'll have the blue silk.
See, that's what
I would've gone for.
Blue silk, Huh?
Jess, I've been
packed for six months
so let's just go.
Let's go. Here we go.
Okay. Kids, that's enough.
That's enough. We've had
a lot of fun, haven't we?
I'm losing my balance.
Kids. Whoo! Kids!
That's enough!
I mean it!
Okay, okay,
clubs down there, kids.
Sorry, Dino, boy.
I guess, having a dinosaur hunt
wasn't such
a hot idea after all.
[laughing]
Hey, everybody, this is it.
Becky's ready to have the twins.
- No!
- Really?
Get outta here.
Don't start that again.
It's true.
I'm gonna have the babies.
At my party? This is better
than Chuck E. Cheese.
Let's go. We've gotta
get to the hospital.
Here, carry this.
Girls, help your Aunt Becky out.
Hey, look,
a dork-a-saurus.
(Danny)
'Out of the way, Kimmy.'
Alright, let's go. Come on,
come on, you guys.
(D.J.)
Becky's having her twins.
Oh, I can help.
My hamster just had triplets.
There's nobody here
but us kids?
That could never happen.
It's true.
We're all alone.
Aah!
[all screaming]
Let's eat birthday cake!
Freeze!
First, I need to make a wish
and blow out the candles.
Is anybody allowed
to play with matches?
(all)
No!
Me neither.
I have to pretend.
Enough already!
Cut the cake.
Is anybody allowed
to use a knife?
(all)
No!
I'll cut the cake.
I take karate.
Hi-yah!
Let's pig out!
[kids giggling]
Oh, no.
We're too late.
- Yum.
Sorry, Michelle, in all
the new baby excitement
I completely forgot
about you and your friends.
That's okay.
Have some cake.
Oh, have some cake.
[instrumental music]
Alright, clear the path.
Woman in labor here.
Move, move, move!
Jess, why don't you just
stick a sign on my back
that says wide load?
You're three weeks early. I
didn't have time to make a sign.
We need a wheelchair.
Hey, look at that,
Doogie Howser.
Excuse me. Here we go. Sit down
here in the wheelchair.
Forgive him.
He's basically lost it.
Hey, excuse me, pardon me,
we need some service here.
Well, how long
have you been walking erect?
Very funny.
Look, I'm having twins here.
I need some service.
Can you call a bellhop?
Would you like
a poolside room
or an ocean view?
Honey, would you like a poolside
room or an ocean view?
- Jess, she was kidding.
- Psst. I knew that.
Fill out these forms..
I mean, would you
care to register?
Sorry I'm late.
I had little trouble getting my
tail through the revolving door.
(Kimmy)
'Mr. T..'
...people are staring.
Lose the lizard suit.
Why should I?
I look fabulous in lavender.
I'm really
into this character.
The truth is,
I'm not wearing any pants.
You're not wearing any pants?
Gross!
Kimmy, do me a favor. Call home
and tell 'em everything's okay.
You got a quarter?
Where would I keep it?
Call collect and tell them
to please bring some pants.
Right. Bring pants.
Because he's not wearing any!
Would Puff the Magic Dragon
like a hospital gown?
Actually, I'd love one.
And the name is Dino.
- Come with me.
- Hm.
(woman on PA)
'Dr. Irvine, call
nurses' station..'
- Hi, Rebecca.
- Oh, hi, doctor.
Your birthing room's
all ready. How you doing?
Fine. The contractions
are seven minutes apart.
- Good.
- Mine are every time I breathe.
What do you mean?
She says I'm having
sympathy pains
but would I have them
right around this black spot?
You mind if I take a look?
Ow!
Jesse, I'm afraid, you may
need to have your appendix out.
- Now?
- What?
No, no, no. I can't have
my appendix taken out.
I'm going into labor.
I want you to see Dr. Larkin
in emergency right away.
- Orderly, I need a wheelchair--
- I'm not going anywhere.
I'm gonna stay right here
with my wife.
Honey, that's very sweet
but you're gonna do
what the doctor says.
How serious is this?
Well, it's fairly routine
but it's something
we need to take care of now.
- Have a seat, Jesse.
- I don't believe this.
Jess, what's going on?
Are you okay?
Oh, sure. I'm fine.
Just figured, heck,
while I'm here
might as well have
my appendix taken out.
Can't you just let
Becky have the babies?
You are so competitive.
You think I wanted
this to happen now?
Listen, doctor, if I have
to go into surgery
am I gonna be back
in time to help my wife?
There's no way to know.
You need to sit down.
Danny, listen, if I don't
make it out in time
can you, uh, help coach
Becky through the childbirth?
Ah, Jess, no problem. I've been
through this three times before.
I could do this with
one hand behind my back.
Which I may have to,
to keep this gown closed.
Beck, I'll be back
as soon as possible.
Try to wait as long
as you can to have the twins.
I'll do my best.
I'm sorry, Beck.
There's no place
in the world I'd rather be
than right here with you.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Hurry back, honey.
Wait for me.
Nice buns.
[instrumental music]
Yes, I know you
just dropped your son off
but it's amazing how much fun
you can cram into 15 minutes.
Uh-huh. Okay, bye.
Okay, kids, your parents are
on their way to pick you up.
We've to reach the hospital
before the babies are born.
So let's wait for 'em
out on the porch!
Move it, people.
The party's over.
But you never
opened your presents.
Hold it, people.
The party's back on.
Okay, kids. We're gonna
play a new game now.
It's called, Open the Present
You Brought as Fast as You Can.
How do you play?
Well, you open the present
you brought as fast
as you can, hence the name
Open the Present You Brought
as Fast as You Can.
I think I get it now.
Okay, everybody,
get in a straight line.
Alright.
Now, ready, get set..
'...open the present
you brought as fast as you can!'
'Alright, there we are.
We're opening.'
'We're having a great time.'
'Oh, good. Look how fast
this guy's going.'
'Oh, good.
It looks beautiful.'
That's it, great.
(Joey)
'Those are some
beautiful presents.'
Now, hold them out so Michelle
can see what she got.
Love it. Love it.
Love it. Like it.
Love it.
Like it. Love it.
That looked bigger on TV.
And that officially
ends the party.
Please place your presents
gently on the floor
and proceed
to the nearest exit.
Okay, that would be this way.
Have a nice day.
And don't forget, buckle up.
Come on.
Thanks for the presents
and thanks for coming.
This was a strange party.
[exhaling sharply]
♪ We will
we will rock you.. ♪
- Whoo whoo hee.
- 'Sing it!'
♪ We.. ♪♪
I'm sorry.
Becky, just keep
breathing, okay?
We're almost
through this one.
Okay? The main thing
is not to think about the pain.
There is no pain. Pain is not
part of your vocabulary.
Pain does not exist.
Danny, do you think
you could say the word pain
just a few more times?
I'm sorry, I'm just trying
to help keep your mind off
that not-so-great feeling.
[exhales sharply]
[knock on door]
(Joey)
'Are you ready for us?'
Come on in, everybody.
Did you have the twins yet?
- No, not yet.
- What's taking 'em so long?
Maybe they can't decide
who should come out first.
Well, it could take a while.
According to my biology teacher
a woman can be
in labor for days.
[sobbing]
Where's Jess?
As it turned out, his
stomach ache was appendicitis.
- Is he gonna be alright?
- I'm sure he'll be fine.
He just has to have
an appendectomy.
Appen...what?
Well, boys and girls,
in scientific terms
an appendectomy is when they
take that little thingamajig
out of your tum-tum
that you really don't need-need.
Hey, everybody.
Great news.
Kimmy, is Jesse okay?
I don't know.
I got lost.
But I did find Luke
this really cute guy
with two broken arms.
So I volunteered
to spoon-feed him his Jell-O.
Is Uncle Jessie gonna
miss the babies being born?
Oh, I hope not.
I really want him to be here.
Oh, don't you worry, Beck
'cause either way, he's gonna
get to see the birth.
Excuse me.
Alright.
Come on in, guys.
Danny, what is this?
Becky, it's
your own camera crew.
You know Mark and Eppie.
I know who they are.
What are they doing in my room?
Don't you remember when you
announced you were pregnant
on "Wake Up, San Francisco?"
You promised all of our viewers
that we'd get to see
the whole thing on tape.
Yeah, well, that's when
I was thin, my hair was done
and I wasn't sweating.
That's not sweat.
That's a mother's glow.
Come on, let's do
a quick little intro
before your next
contraction, huh?.
- Danny, I am not gonna do this.
- We're rolling.
Hi, I'm Rebecca Donaldson
and I'm in labor.
And I am Danny Tanner.
and right now, we are in
Rebecca's very hospital room
where she's about
to give birth to twins.
I'm gonna be here
every second coaching Becky
through her delivery and giving
you the play-by-play
as we all watch in amazement
the miracle of life.
[chuckles]
Well, Danny, about that miracle
it's kinda a private thing
that I'll be happy to talk
about wit you when I return
to the show in a few weeks.
But until then, this is
Rebecca Donaldson saying..
...get out of my room.
[chuckles]
And cut.
[instrumental music]
[exhales sharply]
You're doing great, Rebecca.
It's not gonna be long now.
Oh, I wish Jesse
were here with me.
[exhales sharply]
[breathes deeply]
Oh, okay.
That one's over.
Oh, man, that was
the toughest contraction yet.
Gee, Danny,
maybe you should lie down.
No, Becky.
I've made it this far.
I'm gonna go all the way.
Sponge.
Thanks.
[knock on door]
Jesse's out of surgery.
- Is he okay?
- The surgery went fine.
Oh, Jess!
You made it
just when I need you.
This is a pretty room.
He's still a little groggy
from the anesthesia.
Jess, I just want you to know
you should be
really proud of Becky.
She's doing
a really great job.
Hey, I know you.
- You're, uh..
- Danny.
No, that's not it.
You guys need us
for anything else?
No, we'll take it
from here. Thanks.
Hey, you've been a really
great coach. Thanks.
Anytime.
Thank you, Donny.
Close enough.
Oh, honey, I'm so glad
you made it in time.
In time for what?
The birth of our babies.
Oh, that's right.
You're having my baby.
♪ What a lovely way ♪
♪ Of saying
how much you love me.. ♪♪
Jess, just hold my hand.
Won't your husband
Donny be jealous?
Jess, you're my husband.
I get a wife and a baby
in the same day.
Radical!
♪ Havin' my baby.. ♪♪
Okay, Rebecca, here comes
another contraction.
- We're gonna push on this one.
- Okay.
(female #1)
'Get ready, deep breath..'
'...and push!'
- Ooh!
- Aah!
Whoa! Whoa!
'Good girl.'
♪ Havin' my baby.. ♪
'Six, good girl!'
♪ What a lovely way of saying
what you're thinking of me.. ♪
'Three. Come on!'
♪ Havin' my baby ♪♪
'You're doing great,
I can see the head!'
'Come on, Rebecca!'
- Whoa!
- Shut up!
Beck, I'm so proud of you.
Oh, honey, look what
we brought into this world.
Thank you for giving me two
beautiful, healthy little boys.
[Rebecca chuckling]
Look at him smile.
I love you.
I love you, too.
And thank you for making this
the happiest day of my life.
I can't believe it.
I'm the father
of two identical twin sons.
Hey.
Hey, bub, I'm your daddy.
And I'm your mommy.
Hi.
Becky, can you believe it?
We're parents.
How are we doing
so far, dad?
I think they dig us.
Hey, look at this.
They got your little nose.
And they have
your cute smile.
How'd they end up
with Fred Mertz' hair?
You guys feel up
for some visitors?
Sure. Come on in.
Come on, everybody.
(all)
Aw.
- Hi, family.
- Hi, everybody.
[high pitch]
Hi, little baby boys.
My name is Joey
and I'm gonna teach you
how to do archery
bowling, hockey, race cars--
Joey, Joey, they just
learned to open their eyes.
[high pitch]
Okay, then,
we'll just play peek-a-boo.
[chuckling]
And, guys,
I'm your Uncle Danny.
I don't do any funny voices,
but thanks to me
your diapers are going
to smell April Fresh.
What are their names?
Well, we each
got to pick a name.
So, I picked Alexander,
after my high school teacher
who gave me the inspiration
to go into journalism.
And I picked Nicholas,
after my father
who gave me great hair.
You hear that, baldy?
Grow, grow.
Which one is which?
We don't know yet.
Alright, who wants
to be Alexander?
[belches]
We have a volunteer.
They look exactly alike.
How are you gonna
tell 'em apart?
You could put a drop of red nail
polish on one of their backs.
That's what I did
with my turtles.
Your babies
are very cute.
You get two thumbs up.
Thank you, Michelle.
They're so little, they could
wear my doll's clothes.
Hey, back off, shorty.
They're boys.
Michelle, we're really sorry
you had to cut your
birthday party short.
It's cool.
Well, Michelle, just think,
now you get to share
your birthday with the twins.
That means triple birthdays.
Is that a good thing?
Well, you get three
birthday cakes.
That's a very good thing.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday,
dear Michelle ♪
♪ Alex and Nicky ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪♪
♪ Ahhh ahh ahh ahhh ♪
[theme music]
♪ Chity Chi bob botta ♪♪